<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Projects on Portfolio website for Max Derie</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Projects on Portfolio website for Max Derie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Around the world in 80 drinks</title>
      <link>/blogs/alcohol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/alcohol/</guid>
      <description>Where Do People Drink The Most Beer, Wine And Spirits?Drinking alcoholic beverages is an important part of culture in many parts of the world. Whether it is to celebrate, close a deal, cool down or simply to come to rest, people have become adept at finding opportunities and reasons to start drinking. However, the type of beverage and general drinking culture can vary greatly from place to place. Even in Europe, major differences can be found between the wine-tasting South, beer consuming North and spirits in the East.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid deaths in Belgium</title>
      <link>/blogs/covidbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/covidbe/</guid>
      <description>Throughout 2020, the covid-19 virus tore through the world and affected all sections of the population. It is, however, undeniable that some layers were affected more than others. This analysis involves an investigation into the demographic characteristics of deaths related the the covid virus pandemic of 2020 in Belgium, with the aim of achieving insight in which sections of the population are the most susceptible.
First, let us inspect the provided data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demographics and Brexit-results</title>
      <link>/blogs/brexit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/brexit/</guid>
      <description>Demographic analysis of Brexit resultsIn the middle of 2016, the outcome of the Brexit referendum held in the UK shook Europe, as it would have lasting consequences on the relation between the UK and the rest of the European Union. On this page, we take a look at the results of the Brexit votes across different constituencies in Britain, and analyse the influence of different demographic parameters. This will allow us to gain insights in what motives that motioned the British people to vote for a break from the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering</title>
      <link>/blogs/engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/engineering/</guid>
      <description>Modelling in mechanical engineeringHaving graduated a master’s degree in mechanical engineering with great distinction, I have acquired extensive knowledge in building and analysing mathematical models of real-life systems. In this folder, I provide links to multiples studies that I have performed through my university carreer. In stead of gathering measurement data and performing a regression analysis to extract a working model, the approach taken in these works is rather the opposite: going out from fundamental physical laws and previously established models of subsystems, a working model of the entire system is created.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>